(echoing):
To Mars!
(Sheldon:)Afterwards,
Leonard blew his nose,
(Sheldon:)and pie came out.
LEONARD:
Right there, right there,
Oh, God, that's it!
(Penny:)How did you get paint
in your eye?
(Leonard:)Because you wouldn't let me
wear safety goggles!
(sighs heavily)
This looks terrible.
She-she's gonna know.
(Howard:)It's fine.
(Howard:)You just need two more nails.
(Raj:)Okay, where should I put them?
(Howard:)In Emily's eyes.
(Raj:)You're not helping.
(Bernadette:)Well, maybe this is
what you get for snooping.
You know, it-it's bad enough
that I have to deal with this...
EMILY:
Raj? I'm back.
(door closes)
(Raj:)Oh, no.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hi.
(stammering):
How was the hospital?
(Amy:)Fine.
(Emily:)What were you doing in there?